quiz_questions = [
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of France?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Paris",
                "id_question": "1",
                "correct": True
            },
            {
                "answer": "London",
                "id_question": "2",
                "correct": False
            },
            {
                "answer": "New York",
                "id_question": "3",
                "correct": False
            },
            {
                "answer": "Berlin",
                "id_question": "4",
                "correct": False
            }
        ]
    },
    # {
    #     "question": "What is the capital of Czechia?",
    #     "answers": [
    #         {
    #             "answer": "Prague",
                
    #             "id_question": "5",
    #             "correct": True
    #         },
    #         {
    #             "answer": "London",
    #             "id_question": "6",
    #             "correct": False
    #         },
    #         {
    #             "answer": "New York",
    #             "id_question": "7",
    #             "correct": False
    #         },
    #         {
    #             "answer": "Berlin",
    #             "id_question": "8",
    #             "correct": False
    #         }
    #     ]
    # }
]


def get_quiz_questions():
    return quiz_questions